Hello hello friends welcome to my YouTube
channel friends today we will talk about VIP
Industries Restaurants Media Consumer
Products ICICI Lombard General
Insurance Indian Container Corporation of
India and friends
subscribe so friends let's start
friends if you
want to subscribe then you can
click on the link in the link description box
after that you can
subscribe to any channel like subscribe to the channel
subscribe and
subscribe friends now the school's
high price was 766 rupees that friends
VIP Industries' symbol was 727 and
subscribe and share so friends
Restaurants
appointed friends
150 rupees friends
subscribe friends now we will talk about Tata
Consumer Products so friends this
time the product which is
225 friends subscribe of Consumer Products is the
most paisa per one pan friends now
we will talk about ICICI Lombard General
Insurance so friends ICICI
Direct has ICICI Lombard General
Insurance product
265 1550 friends ICICI Lombard
General Insurance
1275 subscribe
friends
1390 paisa friends that
war friends like war
subscribe friends
subscribe to
150  Friends, now we will talk about Container
Corporation of India, so friends Anand
Rathi has Container Corporation of India
Pride and
subscribe friends subscribe to Container Corporation of
India,
friends now we will talk
friends subscribe to the channel
friends
subscribe friends
Industries Limited,
tell us in the comment subscribe to our channel
like the video
thanks for watching the